

0745 49 59 70





SKILLS

WEB DESIGN GRAPHIC DESIGN **DRAWING** CSS ANIMATION JQUERY Magento frontend VUE GIT

HOBBIES

Photography

CSS/JS Animations

Music

Movies

Cooking

Alexandru Dan GATEA

UI/UX DEVELOPER

Experienced UI/UX Developer with high focus on output quality and user experience. Extensive knowledge in HTML, CSS Frameworks, Material and Atomic Design Patterns, latest CSS technologies and approaches. Solid experience in jQuery, Javascript, user interaction patterns. Good skills with developing jQuery and Javascript solutions to improve user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE



CURRICULUM VITAE

May. 2015 - Present

3y, 8m

UI/UX Developer & UI Tech Lead | Digital Republic

- create wireframes and templates for various projects
- build web elements using HTML5, CSS, SASS, LESS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Own SCSS framework
- atomic design development patterns
- create print materials for advertising purposes
- offer technical support for design problems
- create brand identity manuals, including logos, business cards, color palettes
- create icon fonts
- assesing, coordinating and developing web interfaces as well as trainging and managing fellow UI passionates

Apr. 2014 - Mar. 2015

Graphic Designer | Student Plus Association

Responsabilities: creating concepts for advertising materials such as posters, banners, certificates, tickets, covers, simulations, presentations for events like TiMAF, James Blunt, Absolvire de la A la Z, OmniPass

Oct. 2010 - Nov. 2013

3y, 1m

11m. 14d

Graphic Designer | FAS-USAMV Cluj-Napoca

Responsabilities: creating concepts for advertising materials such as banners, posters, facebook covers, tickets and roll-ups for weekly student parties, Proms, Educational Projects.

EDUCATION



Oct. 2013 - Jun. 2015

Masters

Processing Systems and Food Quality Control

USAMV Cluj-Napoca, Faculty of Food Science and Technology

Oct. 2009 - Jul. 2013

Bachelor's degree - Food Industry Engineer

Food Quality Control

USAMV Cluj-Napoca, Faculty of Food Sciences and Technology

Sept. 2005 - Jul. 2009

High School Diploma

Technical College of Aiud, Mathematics & Informatics Studied: Mathematics, Informatics, English, Physics.

PERSONAL SKILLS



Communication skills

Sociable, good communicating competences along with team spirit.

Organizational/ managerial skills Dynamic person, punctual, sense of responsibility, perfectionism, thoroughly, good competences in organizing a team.

Job related skills

Great time management, organized, agile, perseverance.

Computer skills

Advanced knowledge on HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, jQuery, Git. I've also worked with: Bootstrap, Materialize, UI KIt, Laravel, Magento 2, Vue, npm, yarn, ionic.

Advanced knowledge on using Adobe Photoshop CC, Illustrator CC,

Adobe XD; basic knowledge of Adobe InDesign CC.

Certificate on operating on Microsoft Office™ 2007/2010 (Word,

PowerPoint, Excel, Publisher, Access, Outlook.

Other competences

Driving Licence

Passionate of graphic design, nature photography, cooking, arts (Music, Opera, Photography)

ADDITIONAL INFO



Articles

Co-writer of "Marketing study for chocolate consumption in

Cluj-Napoca"

References References can be offered on request.

